{
    "subject": "resource/Ivesia_pickeringii",
    "predicate": "property/binomialAuthority",
    "object": "Torr. ex Gray",
    "human_readable": "Ivesia pickeringii was described by Torr. ex Gray.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9447984099388123,
            "question": "Who described Ivesia pickeringii?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8370185494422913,
            "question": "What is the full name of the person who described Ivesia pickeringii?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7116492390632629,
            "question": "What plant species was described by Torr. ex Gray?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6976381540298462,
            "question": "What characteristics define Ivesia pickeringii?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.650358259677887,
            "question": "Are there other plants described by Torr. ex Gray?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6463220119476318,
            "question": "Where is Ivesia pickeringii found?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.578433632850647,
            "question": "Is Ivesia pickeringii a type of flower?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5165256261825562,
            "question": "Can you provide more information about Ivesia pickeringii?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4667796790599823,
            "question": "What field is Torr. ex Gray known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4452136158943176,
            "question": "Is Ivesia pickeringii a rare plant?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Ivesia pickeringii was described by Torr. ex Gray.",
            "html": "dbpedia_574_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What field is Torr. ex Gray known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_574_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you provide more information about Ivesia pickeringii?",
            "html": "dbpedia_574_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Ivesia pickeringii a type of flower?",
            "html": "dbpedia_574_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_574_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_574_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_574_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_574_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_574_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_574_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_574_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_574_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_574_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_574_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other triples you'd like me to evaluate!  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "The triple to evaluate is:\n\nIvesia pickeringii was described by Torr. ex Gray.\n\nFrom the provided context, we can see that there are multiple mentions of \"Torr. ex A. Gray\" and \"A. Gray\", but only one mention specifically mentioning Ivesia pickeringii as being described by Torr. ex Gray:\n\n\"...Ivesia pickeringii Torr. ex A. Gray is a synonym...\"\n\nThis confirms that Ivesia pickeringii was indeed described by Torr. ex Gray.\n\nTherefore, the response should be:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe information provided in the documents supports that \"Ivesia pickeringii\" is a species that was described by Torrejon (Torr.) and Gray, as seen from the synonym description stating \"Ivesia pickeringii Torr. ex A. Gray\"."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}